[rap music playing
over the radio]
[distant siren wailing]
Hey, what y'all trying to grab?
[Diego] Fuck, bro, I'm cool.
That Zorro's fucked me up
last night, bro.
That shit gave me
the pure bubble guts.
I really need to find
a duck-off spot ASAP.
Damn.
You should've stuck with
your regular carne asada, nigga.
[chuckles] You know
you're not supposed to eat
no shrimp burrito at 2:00 a.m.
[Cloudy] Stanky-ass nigga, bro.
Don't let that shit slide out
your ass too, bro.
[Diego] Man,
fuck both of y'all, bro.
- I really need to--
- Hey, hey, stop right quick.
- [Diego] The fuck you doing?
- I'mma wack this nigga out.
[Juju panting]
[Cloudy] Hold up, fam.
That's how you rocking,
young nigga?
- Shit.
- Man, I seen that nigga drop
that shit in his backseat.
I would terrorize him
in parking there.
Let's see...
[Cloudy] Yo, dude.
Looking like baby Cloudy.
[Cloudy laughs]
[chill music playing]
[news reporter]
In sports, the International
Basketball League
was busy last night with
seven games on the schedule.
The Cavaliers came up
with a surprise upset,
beating the Bullets
108 to 99.
The Lakers had no trouble
with the Rockets,
winning 124 to 88.
- The Nuggets just got...
- Oh.
[news reporter
continues indistinctly]
Look at my lip gloss.
Look at it. [smooches]
It's clear, it's new.
[exhales]
[sighs]
Baby.
Baby, what's wrong?
[kissing]
- [Slim] Oh, oh.
- [moans softly]
I think the only one
who should be worried is me.
Hmm? What do you mean?
Well, a smart...
[kissing]
...sexy basketball player
like you?
You could have
anything you want.
Anyone you want.
Dee, get on with that shit.
You saying anything.
You know
it's just me and you.
No other bitch for me.
Good.
There better not be.
Mm, come here.
Also, you my fucking queen,
all right?
[Slim] Mmm.
You feel that?
[chuckles]
Why don't you show daddy
how much you love him?
- Okay, daddy.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, bro-- Oh, shit!
- Yo, yo! What the fuck?
- Oh, my bad.
- Nigga, you don't know
- how to knock?
- Ah, shit, uh, y'all two
are always fucking,
so I-I figured
you might lock the door
this time.
Uh, what you want, man?
Maybe a, "Hey, Ju.
Uh, what's up, bro?"
Something, something. [chuckles]
Oh, shit.
- [Destiny chuckles]
- Hey, Destiny.
- How you feelin'?
- Ju. I'm good.
- Yo. Hey, hey. Come on.
- [Destiny] Okay.
- [Destiny giggles]
- [clicks tongue]
- Come on, bro. Come on.
- Shit.
- [exhales]
- [controllers clicking]
Man, you always playing
this fucking song.
Uh, Mom been home yet?
Nah, not yet.
Said she working
a double tonight,
be here in the morning.
Where you been at?
I don't know why
you don't answer your phone.
- You know it pisses her off.
- I know.
I know.
Shit, I've been outside.
Getting into shit?
Yeah.
What's in the bag?
[Juju] Oh, none of your...
none of your fucking business.
Oh, shit!
Yo, look at
all these letters!
Yo, you can go
anywhere you want, bruh.
I mean, shit,
he gonna be the next Kobe
or-- or Michael Jordan,
even better. Shit!
[Juju and Destiny dapping]
[Juju] What's up, bruh?
Eli, you that boy, okay?
[chuckles] You got
the whole city backing you,
'cause you badass.
All right? So, shit, relax.
Enjoy that shit.
Okay? Shit, I am.
Yo, you coming with me
to practice tomorrow?
I got an interview
with The Thizzler.
Whoo!
Hey, a few scouts
and other reporters
- are gonna be there too.
- Word?
Yo, I need you.
For sure.
Say less, bro.
- That's hella dope. Shit.
- Yes, sir. Thanks, bro.
- You know I'm in that.
- All right.
Man, get your shit
and get out.
- Bye, Dee.
- Bye, boo.
- [Slim] Yo, Ju.
- What's up?
Text Mom. That way,
she knows you're home
and ain't tripping, all right?
For sure.
[Slim] Yo, I mean it!
- [both chuckling]
- ["Up!" by IAMSU! playing]
- [Slim] Bring that ass
here, girl.
- [Destiny squeals]
[chuckling]
[song fades out]
[dog barking in distance]
[men chattering in distance]
[chuckling] I knew
your ass wasn't down.
[chuckles]
You're dumb, bro.
[car passes]
What?
Whoa.
Yo, are you serious?
Yeah, bro.
[Juju gasps, sniffles]
I do.
- [laughing] Give me my--
- I do.
Give me my shit, boy.
- Yo, you for real though?
- [sighs]
Yeah.
She been tripping about me
leaving and all.
She my ride or die, bro.
And I really need your help
with the surprise.
Hell yeah.
[Slim chuckles]
- Yes, sir.
- Tss.
- My brother getting married.
- Yeah, I'm getting married.
What? [chuckles]
Hey, I'm not wearing
a tux though.
Oh, you definitely
gonna be in a suit.
- What?
- Yeah, hands down,
- you gonna be in a suit.
- I'll fight it till the day.
Look, you know what?
It's a celebration
tonight.
- Yeah, celebrate. Shit.
- [sighs]
[Slim] Mm.
You tell Mom?
[Slim exhales]
[Preach] Hey, bro, like I said,
it really get bangy out here.
Don't be taking them pills.
My young life
out there in West Point
got hit
with the fentanyl.
Bro was on them pills.
Nigga dead?
The hell you think
I'm telling the story for?
Of course, he dead,
dummy.
- Damn!
- What?
Why is the nigga making a mess
all over the whole Corona for?
Nigga is crazy
right here.
This ain't even your whip.
Whose bucket
is this anyway, nigga?
Who gives a shit,
asshole?
W-what about
yesterday bip?
Yeah, little snow bunny.
What she say?
- "Oh, my baby in the car.
- [laughs]
- Stop! Help!"
- Y'all some demons, bruh.
- [laughing]
- Demons, bruh.
If I was Juju, man,
I would've had to smack
the shit
out of the bitch, man.
Homie getting soft on us,
I'm telling you.
Somebody tell Juju
to hurry the fuck up too, man,
'cause I--
I ain't finna be waiting
for this nigga forever,
dog.
[Cloudy] Freaky dicky nigga
probably tryin' to rub
one out before he come out.
He sure thinkin'--
[Preach] Hey, nigga,
I said two minutes!
- I called you
two minutes ago, bro!
- [Juju] Hey, bro.
Chill, chill, chill.
It's a neighborhood.
[Preach] Nigga,
bring your ass outside.
Fuck your neighborhood.
[Monique] Juju. [knocks]
You awake?
[somber music playing]
[news alert tune playing]
[news reporter
reporting indistinctly]
[grunts]
Morning, baby.
You better be
getting ready soon.
You got a big day of training
ahead of you.
Just know,
anything you do
is dope.
Look...
whatever you decide
is gonna be the right decision.
You know that.
[chuckles softly]
[news alert tune plays]
[sports broadcaster
speaking indistinct]
Just take a look around.
We didn't get here
without all the hard work
and sacrifice.
You know how proud I am
to know that my baby,
born and raised in the city,
about to make it out. [chuckles]
[Mellow] Hey, yo.
I know you ain't t--
You texting
Ms. Johnson's fine ass?
All right, bro.
Shit.
[laughing]
Man, shit, you are not lying.
Make sure you text her back,
bro, for real.
'Cause if she hitting my phone
looking for you again,
it's over.
I'm pulling up
and I'm playing step-pops, bro.
You might as well
call me "Uncle Phil."
[laughing]
- Big fuck you.
- Who they talking about?
- Y'all talking about Ju's mom?
- Oh...
- Hey. Hey, listen, listen.
- Fuck off. What?
I ain't gonna lie,
bruh.
- She is bad as fuck.
- All right, nigga.
- Yeah, fuck y'all. All right?
- I'm telling you, bro.
Oh, shit,
check this out.
All right.
So my bro,
he finna propose
to Dee today.
Man, what the fuck
he doing that for?
This nigga is on the verge
of getting all the pussy
a nigga could ever dream of.
And he gonna go all
"Captain Save A Hoe"
on a nigga?
Like, for real,
he gonna go save the bitch, bro.
[Diego]
Fucked up.
[Mellow] Tone pulling up.
What's happening, Tone?
I see y'all homies out there
doing your thing, man,
making these moves.
Yeah,
I fuck with it, man.
Make sure you stay on top
of our business though.
Tighten up ship,
you know what I mean?
All right, man,
I'm gonna get back
in motion, man.
Pull up to the Velvet room
if you need me, bro.
Yo, be safe, man,
all right?
All right, for sure.
[Mar] Some real Mexican
gangster shit here.
- [Diego] Yeah, bruh.
- You feel me?
Seen that bitch
he pulled up with?
[Diego] Man,
fine than a motherfucker.
That boy don't listen
for shit. [scoffs]
Smelling good
in here.
[Monique] Your damn brother
gonna give me a heart attack.
He's young.
You know
he gonna figure it out.
[Monique] Mm-hmm.
[Slim] I know
you ain't feeling
his friends
and you know
I feel the same way,
you feel me?
But...
I mean, he got
his head on straight.
I just know how he gets
when I get in his ear
too much.
[Slim] Hmm.
- [utensils clatter]
- Mom, don't trip.
- You know I got it.
- We just gotta get him
to help out
around the house, son.
I know.
I'll get at it.
[sips]
[Monique] Oh! Uh...
This better not be
what I think it is.
Um, she been tripping
that when I leave,
I'mma leave her behind.
She's all I want, Mom.
[sighs]
Just make sure you making
the right move, okay?
You always worrying.
I got this.
I know you do, baby.
- Mm.
- Now, get your ass outta here
and get to practice.
All right, all right.
I'mma get going.
- [kisses] Love you, Mom.
- Hmm. I love you too.
[Slim] Oh.
[sips] Ahh.
Ah, ah, ah!
Don't forget your little ring.
[Slim] Oh, shit.
[chuckles]
[Preach] This is my spot.
Feeling I'm finna crams.
It's where I always hit.
Keep my head on a swivel.
Feel me?
You would be surprised
how much shit
these niggas leave
in their whips, bro.
Like, bruh, like,
not even wallets and shit.
We just talking about
random shit.
Nigga got spooked
and left this in the glove box.
Yeah. [chuckles]
Homie came up to me
trying to stop me,
like he was about something.
I had to give it to him.
He took
that ass whopping though.
He lucky
I ain't had a hammer on me.
And, bruh,
these white boys,
they be up there
in Silicon Valley
living it up.
[knocking on door]
Ah, shit!
- What's good, bro?
- My guy.
Come on. Let me show you
how we get down.
[chill hip-hop music playing]
[Preach] House looking
like traps. Traps!
Like, straight up.
Hoes selling pussy,
selling stolen merch,
running it up on the internet.
These white boys
be wildin'.
Crazy.
...really need
to hurry his ass up.
[Preach] Let me tell you
about my nigga, Styles.
We really be in the field
splashing for this pay.
Nigga gotta get it
by any means necessary.
This area we headed to
right here, everything goes.
From electronics,
hygiene product,
wild D nigga, clothes,
even baby formula.
And a nigga'll sell they mama
down here if they could.
[man] Hey, yo, let me see
what you got, brother.
Let me see.
[Styles] Fuck you mean, man?
You know, laptops and things.
[man] Oh, yeah,
oh, yeah.
How much you want?
Twenty-five, man.
That's all we can go,
man, 25...
- Twenty-five, man.
- We all gotta eat, brother.
We all gotta eat.
Bro, I'm the one
running around
and shit, man.
Twenty-five, man.
Come on.
[man] Shit.
What's the lowest,
brother?
- What's the lowest?
- Two.
Let's do two, bruh.
- I'll give you a grand.
I'll give you a grand.
- Two, so--
You gotta meet me
halfway, cousin.
- Two. Meet me halfway.
- [Preach] Fifteen.
[man]
Fifteen hundred? Bet.
It's for the one time,
'cause I fuck with y'all,
y'all know.
Hey, that's my man
right here.
Told you to fuck with it
every time.
[man]
It's how it is.
You know
we gonna be right back,
right back though type shit,
you hear me?
Take care of the little ones
and shit like that, man.
- Get me right, man.
- [man] Yeah.
Fifteen right here.
Nice doing business with you.
All right, we outta here.
- [man] Mm-hmm.
- [Styles indistinct]
Bro, I got a homie
from the Rich,
he just hit for a hundred.
- Stacks, bands.
- [Cloudy] A hundred?
First of all,
any nigga touching
that much chicken
is not leaving that nowhere,
brother. I promise you.
- [Preach] Hmm.
- [Diego] White nigga might.
Hey, where was you at?
You was there?
Oh, I ain't know you was there.
Where was you at, bro?
Why you ain't hit me, man?
- Probably at the bitch house.
- Yeah, shut your ass up, nigga.
You wasn't there. You ain't
really tap in like that.
My money up, bro.
What you got?
What's in there?
[Cloudy] I'm saying...
[Preach] Oh, that's it!
That's a little cake!
- You can see that ten.
- Hey, hey.
There's some tens
in there.
You see the blues though?
Y'all ain't nothin'.
Like I said, bruh,
keep your head
on a swivel, man.
- [car horn honks]
- [Mellow] Yo!
Let's hit the mall.
[Diego]
I'm about to ride with him.
See what these pieces
talking about, you feel me?
[sighs]
[compartment closes]
Well, Slim, you the talk
of the city right now.
Go to any college you want to.
Can probably go straight
to the league.
What's next?
I'm blessed to be
in the position I'm in.
Oh, my God,
he's doing so good. He's--
- Do you think he's nervous?
- Ain't a lot of us
had the opportunity
to get out of the mud.
You know what I mean?
They call this
"the player's graveyard."
I'm just blessed to ball
the way I do.
But it took a lot of hard work
and sacrifice
from a lot of people
to get me here.
- That's real.
- [coach] Hey, all-star,
let's wrap this up.
You gonna have plenty of years
to do interviews.
Go make the city proud, man.
Hey, I appreciate it,
bruh.
Oh, shit.
Weapon up in here.
[whispers indistinct]
[Juju] Yo,
what's happenin'?
- [P-Lo] This shit
going silver, bro.
- Oh, shit.
Is that P-Lo?
You never disappoint,
man.
[Mellow] Yeah,
that's that nigga, cuz.
- Quit fanboying now.
- [Juju] What you mean?
[as Juju, mockingly]
"Is that P-Lo head ass?"
- Man, shut the fuck up.
- [scoffs]
- What's happening with y'all?
- Hey, brother.
What, nigga?
I mean-- [gibbering]
If you don't shut
your goofy ass up...
- Fuck.
- [clicks tongue]
- Nigga ain't paying my bill.
- Trippin'.
[salesperson] Hey,
you find everything okay?
- [Mellow] Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
- How you doing today?
- Not bad.
- Like, uh... Right there.
- Ooh!
I see you two gentlemen
have great taste.
You know a nigga like
the finer things in life,
- you know what I'm saying?
- Yeah, yeah.
Let me get that
right there, player.
- Wanna try it on?
- Nah.
I already know what I like.
[salesperson] All right,
let me box that up for you.
[Mellow] I might get these
for my baby mama.
Mm. Yeah, if you walk up
in the house with the--
- She be trippin' and all.
- [showcase door closes]
- Your, uh...
- Get something for yourself.
...your total's
gonna be $9,860.
Is that gonna be cash or card?
Shit, man.
You know I can't leave the crib
without it.
[laughs] You know.
[Mellow]
Keep runnin' 'em.
Should we start getting
a little bit of this then?
A little bit.
I like those ones.
[Mellow]
I'm trippin'.
[salesperson]
Can I, uh, see
some ID, please?
Of course, you can.
- [Juju] Can I just--
- [chuckles] Niggas act like
they don't know me now.
[salesperson]
Sure. Perfect.
Thank you very much.
- [Juju] I need
to pick something.
- [Mellow] You should get those
for your woman,
you know what I mean?
- That's how you start
getting some ass, bro.
- [error beep]
Gentlemen, you,
by any chance,
have, uh,
another card
you'd like to use?
That thing tripping again?
[salesperson]
Uh, it's no worries.
Sometimes, it happens
on big purchases.
I mean, if you check
your cell phones,
sometimes they're gonna
send you like a fraud alert.
[Mellow] How much you said
it was again?
[salesperson] Uh, $9,680.
- [Mellow] Shit. Oh, shit.
- [chuckles]
- Oh, shit!
- Excuse me, sir.
- You can use that card.
- Dolo.
- What up, my nigga?
- What's up, my niggas?
- Big dog.
- What's up, my guys?
- [Juju] What up, big bro?
- Chilling, man.
- Trying to get like you.
Put a nigga on.
- What's good?
- Hey, man.
- Um... Larry.
Hey, before we wrap
all this shit up,
let me see them earrings
right there, bruh.
[Dolo]
Sheesh!
Bitches gleaming.
[Larry] Good choice.
[Mellow] Mm-hmm. Oh, yeah.
Ooh, let me see
that bust down piece.
Damn, bro.
- This nigga on The Thizzler?
- [Juju] That shit crazy.
The fuck
is you doing here, bro?
Shit got a 100K views.
He was playing, man.
Hey, you supposed to be
right there with that nigga.
Ay, yo, his bro
got a 100K views
in, like, two minutes
at The Thizzler, bro.
- Damn!
- Sheesh.
Your brother
really finna be
that next nigga
- to blow out the city, bro.
- Yeah, man.
- All right.
- Steph Curry in this bitch.
- That's how it is.
- Hey, make sure
you let
that nigga know...
don't fuck this up.
He got this.
- Right.
- This nigga done copped
the watch for me.
Shoot it.
Money.
[hip-hop music playing]
[coach 1]
Oh, go.
Ohh, okay.
- [panting]
- [coach 1] One more.
Pass it.
Work hard, Johnson,
work hard! [clapping]
Go, come on, let's go!
Pick it up, Whitaker, Johnson!
Let's go!
Show 'em!
You can't guard--
[player] Come on! Down here!
[man] Whoo!
[music ends]
[coach 2] Good fucking job, 2-1.
That's what
you supposed to do.
Now, all I need
for you to do
is just come and be ready
for practice, okay?
Uh, about that,
Coach...
See, I got something special
planned for Destiny later,
and, uh...
Look, I was hoping to spend
the rest of the day with her.
You trying to get some ass,
right, and you need
to be impressing them?
But you know what?
Since you did so good today,
I'mma work with you.
Tomorrow, I want you bright
and early here in the morning.
- You hear me? No excuses.
- I'm in.
I'm telling you
what's happening.
- Have fun out here and be safe.
- Yeah, all right.
- Go on.
- Thanks, Coach.
[indistinct] I thought
he was like... for real...
- [Slim] Yo, Dee.
- [Destiny gasps]
[Destiny] Baby!
[chuckles]
You look
so freaking good today.
Yeah! Mm!
- Mm, you're so...
- [Slim chuckles]
Okay, bitch,
we get it.
Let's relax.
Okay, we gotta go get ready
for these college tours.
We gotta go shopping.
We gonna be in LA,
Santa Barbara,
- San Diego, you know?
- [Destiny chuckles]
We gotta look cute
for these college boys.
Look, you don't need
to look good for no one
but me, all right?
Actually,
as a matter of fact,
- I'm gonna steal bae
for a second, all right?
- Okay, but we have plans.
- No, no, I'm gonna steal her.
- I don't have room for this.
What the fuck?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- [Destiny] Fuck me.
Fuck!
- Shit. Hey. Okay, I mean--
- [Mia] Yo, sorry, man.
Look, babe,
this sucks, but--
I'm-- I'm gonna call
my dad's shop. They're--
Baby, it's not that.
It's not that.
- Fuck!
- Baby, everybody gets bipped.
[line ringing]
[Mia] Jesus.
Man, answer
your fucking phone,
nigga!
Fuck!
Damn!
[brakes squeal]
[Destiny]
Baby, wait.
Eli.
[Juju] Pass it back,
pass it back.
- [Destiny] Elijah.
- [Juju] Oh, pass back.
- [man] Shit.
- [Mellow] I thought
he was shitting on you, bro.
Uh, uh!
Hit that.
[Mellow] Curry.
Stephen Curry.
Who the fuck
did you tell, nigga?
- Who the fuck you tell?
- Who the fuck are you talking--
- Yo, bro!
- Who the fuck
is that motherfucker?
Whoa, hold on.
Back the fuck up, bro!
What the fuck
are you talking about?
- Eli--
- [Mellow] Yo,
what is this bullshit?
Y'all supposed
to be brothers, man.
- What y'all acting like
a bunch of bitches for?
- Man, shut the fuck up!
- This shit ain't got nothin'
to do with you.
- [Destiny] Baby, relax...
Unless you want something,
nigga.
Hey, man, look.
I don't want no problems.
You tripping, cuz.
The fuck is going on, bro?
What you tripping so hard for?
Man, I told you
I needed you there today.
You couldn't
even do that.
Nigga, put
the fucking word out
and let 'em know
I ain't playing.
Know who the fuck I am?
[Mellow]
Easy, bro.
Y'all better let everyone know,
even Dolo's ass, nigga.
[Juju] Bro, how could you say
some shit like that
when you know
I got your back?
We brothers.
What the fuck?
Yeah, okay.
Just like you were there
today, right?
- [Destiny] Hey, wait, babe.
- [grunts]
[Destiny sobbing]
[door opens]
There you is, bruh.
I been tapping in
with you, bruh?
Them baby-ass weights and shit.
- [Dolo chuckles]
- What you in here doin'?
This nigga.
[Diego] Hey.
You heard
about Slim, bruh?
- Yeah, what about him?
- Shit.
He been runnin' around
the whole hood
telling everybody to tell you
that he lookin' for your ass.
- [ominous music playing]
- [dumbbell thuds]
- What?
- And the way he talkin',
it's like it's on sight
when he see you.
So the basketball playing nigga
think he a gangster again?
Motherfucking gangster.
Been ridin' around
the whole hood
telling everybody to tell you
that he looking
for your ass specifically.
I would've thought
you been had the drop, nigga.
That bitch-ass nigga better
stick to playing basketball.
- [Diego chuckles]
- Nigga must be mad
somebody bipped his shit.
- Man, Flyer City, my nigga.
- [laughs]
- It happens.
- Fuck that nigga.
You got a fucking lighter?
Y'all here leaving
these big-ass blunts
in this ashtray and shit.
Look, I don't know
what the fuck is going on
between you two here,
but this shit
needs to stop
right now.
[Monique huffs]
Wasting my damn time.
- [thuds]
- [utensils clatter]
Ungrateful asses.
And take that damn hat off
in my house.
I-I don't think
it was Dolo, though.
Weren't y'all like partners
or-- or brothers or some--
I'm gonna stop you there.
Nigga, fuck Dolo!
That nigga slimy.
That shit
ain't gonna get you far.
I have people offering me shit
all the time.
I could take
whatever the fuck I want.
Not everybody got
the same shot you got, right?
God gave you
a gift, bro.
And for the rest of us,
we gotta get it
how we get it.
So, to be real...
that shit don't look like
we doing too bad.
Man, you so fucking stupid,
nigga!
When you gonna open
your eyes, Ju?
Niggas like Dolo gotta sleep
with one eye open.
Is that the lifestyle you want?
[utensils clatter]
Ju, you need to grow
the fuck up, nigga.
[Diego] Hey, y'all remember
that, uh, old girl
from the projects
with the rich mama?
- Yep, I remember that bitch.
- Man, I finally got her
sending me some chicken, bruh.
Uh, G-O-D.
[Diego] Hey, y'all
never know, bruh.
I might be able to retire.
[banging on door]
[Dolo] Who the fuck is that?
Hurry up and grab that shit!
The fuck?
- Move, nigga.
- [Diego] Fuck.
I told you
he was trippin'.
This square-ass nigga.
[door closes]
Aww, shit.
We got a motherfucking all-star
in our presence.
Not too many people know
about this spot.
Surprised you remember.
Not a lot has changed, huh?
[Dolo] That's just it.
Not too many people
wanna switch up.
Some people like for shit
to stay the same way it is.
The fuck you even here for?
You already know
what I'm here for, nigga.
Where the fuck is my ring at?
Why the fuck would I know
about your ring?
Don't fucking play
with me, Do.
I know you know
where my shit is.
Oh, shit.
You got bipped?
[men laughing]
[Diego]
Got his ass.
You left all your shit
in your fucking car.
Why you coming into my spot
with your bullshit?
'Cause I'm saying you keep tabs
on all these dumb-ass
little motherfuckers.
[Dolo] So,
what you calling me?
- A liar...
- Mm.
...or a thief?
Sitting up,
coming in my spot,
talkin' all this shit.
You know what?
Let me tell you something.
You know when you thugging
and shit in the streets, right?
[puffing]
You might hear
some shit.
[liquid pouring]
So, uh...
I heard some shit.
What you gotta do
for me...
save all that built-up
aggression that you got
for the hoop court.
Let the gangsters handle
all the street shit.
I heard the little homie
didn't even know
it was your whip.
You know
how this shit go.
Trying to get
his first splash.
You remember
them days.
Right, nigga?
So if you
fucking remember...
ain't no gettin'
your shit back.
[tense music playing]
So, it is
what it is.
Same old Dolo.
[exhales]
Yeah.
Well, you might have all
these soft-ass niggas fooled.
What you gettin' up for,
nigga?
But I ain't no bitch,
nigga.
Try me,
motherfucker.
[Dolo chuckles]
What you laughing at,
nigga? Huh?
[Dolo] Try you?
You trippin'
on a fucking ring?
For a weak-ass bitch?
[chuckling] Look at
the all-star over here.
Pussy-whipped.
All for
little ol' Destiny.
I don't know why
you trippin' so hard.
You don't remember
back in the day?
We all ran trains
on that bitch.
[grunts]
Back yo ass up!
And what you want,
nigga? Huh?
[Dolo] Jesus.
[laughing]
You don't know
no better, bruh.
All you know how to do
is be a fucking snake.
And I'm good
with that.
So if you think I'm too good
for this shit in here,
maybe I am.
[scoffs]
Clearly, y'all need that shit
more than I do.
Broke-ass bitches.
- [Dolo] Hey, Elijah.
- [gun cocks]
[ominous tone]
[body thuds]
[bullet clinks]
Get rid
of this shit.
Bitch-ass nigga.
♪ Holy presence ♪
♪ Is all in the room ♪
["In The Room (Interlude)"
by Forrest Frank playing]
♪ Oh, the flowing presence ♪
♪ Is all in the room ♪
[song fades out]
[Mellow grunts]
Yo, what's good
with you, bro?
I've been calling your phone.
I even went to your crib
a few times.
You know I ain't good
with this shit, man.
Look, I'm finna tell you
like the OGs told me, bro.
The streets
ain't no joke, bro.
It's crazy people think
it's so sweet out here
'cause all this tech and shit,
knowing damn well
that shit don't benefit
none of us.
It's like every time a nigga
about to make it...
Seem like the streets
just take 'em out.
[sighs] Look,
you my nigga,
G, for real.
Bro, you hear me?
I got your back,
Jules.
No matter what.
Yo.
No matter what,
all right?
[melancholic music playing]
[sighs]
[Destiny crying]
[melancholic music continues]
[door creaking]
[sobs softly]
[music ends]
[rap music playing on speakers]
[cash drawer opens]
[rustling]
[cash drawer closes]
Any pre-roll
for the first visit?
- Nah, you don't, my man.
- Not one?
[annoyed sigh]
Ooh!
Ooh, you know what that is?
Distro van. Here.
I need you to put this
on the bottom of it.
Slap that on there,
it'll teach you a thing or two.
[zipper unzips]
[zips]
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues]
[glass shattering]
[glasses clinking]
[pills clatter]
[inaudible]
[machine whirring]
[club music playing]
[inaudible]
[music fades out]
[Monique]
It's been over a month,
and we still haven't caught
the bastards
who killed my son?
Are you guys even tryin'?
Ma'am, we understand
your concern.
Honestly,
high-profile cases
like this
sometimes take
a bit longer.
Your son, Elijah, was--
is truly something special.
I used to watch
all his highlights.
Ms. Johnson, rest assured
we're doing everything we can
to bring in the suspects.
You have my word.
Okay?
By any chance, is, uh,
your son Julian around?
Is-- is he in trouble
or somethin'?
Because we've already told you
everything that we know.
[dramatic music playing]
[Detective Sanchez] He seems
to be pretty popular in...
some of the circles
we've been talking with.
We were just hoping to see
if there's anything
that comes to mind
that can help us in this case.
That's all.
I'm well aware
of who my son hangs out with,
but he ain't here.
But I'll be sure
to let him know
to give you guys a call.
Thank you for your time.
[music fades out]
[car door closes]
This clown nigga think
he can't get grabbed
right now.
See, that's what
I'm talking about,
brother.
They act like
they run this shit now.
Yeah.
Let me show
you little niggas
how I get down.
- Watch this.
- [Diego] Let's see
what you talking about, bro.
[Preach]
Look at this nigga go.
- What?
- Let me get that shit.
[tense music playing]
- [man] Hey!
- [Dolo] Shit!
Hey, the fuck you doing
to my car?
Ah, fuck this shit!
Fucking
lowlife criminal!
- [glass shattering]
- Fuck you!
This is why I fucking hate
dirty little niggers like you!
- [loud thud]
- [Preach and Diego] Oh, shit!
- [man grunts]
- Fuck!
- [body thuds]
- Nobody talks to me
like that, bitch!
- Nobody!
- [blows landing]
[grunts] Motherfucker!
Fucker! Bitch!
Don't nobody fucking talk
to me like that! Nobody!
- [Diego] Fuck you doin',
nigga?
- [Dolo] Fuck this nigga!
- Let go of me, you nigga!
- [Mellow] Fuck outta here, man.
- [Diego] What the fuck
are you doing?
- [Preach] Move!
- Let's move! Move!
- [Diego] Start the car, nigga!
- Start the car!
- [engine starts]
- [Dolo] Bitch.
- [Diego] Let's go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
[Dolo]
Fuck this bitch-ass nigga.
[Diego] That was
some stupid-ass shit
you did back there.
- What the fuck was that?
- [Dolo] Bro, you should've
let me kill that nigga, man.
- [Preach] You gonna do a nigga
with no mask?
- [Diego] Fuck you, man.
What the fuck
was that?
- [Dolo] Fuck that white boy.
- That was some stupid-ass shit
- you did back there, bruh.
- What? So, you--
you just was gonna do
- a nigga with no mask, Do?
- Yeah, nigga.
- Oh, this nigga right here.
- He act like they won't throw
the book at us
over them fucking white boys!
- [Cloudy] That was
some stupid-ass shit, bruh!
- [Diego] Fuck you, bruh.
Man, what the fuck
are you looking at?
And why
that fucking white boy, bro?
You been tripping
lately, man.
Fuck is wrong
with you?
Look, Mellow,
you wanna let
your fucking nuts hang,
nigga?
You forgetting who run
this shit, huh, nigga?
- [Mellow] Who run it?
- Me!
I'm getting
real fucking sick
of your New York City,
Tri-State Area,
East Coast ass, man.
- [Mellow] Nigga,
bust a move then, man!
- All right, nigga!
- No, he been tripping, bro.
He been fu--
- Hey, bruh, no!
- [Dolo] Shut up your boy, bro!
- Bro.
- [Mellow] You been tripping!
- Y'all niggas is--
Y'all tripping, nigga!
You know that shit was reckless.
You making shit hot,
bro,
when you already
getting paper, nigga!
Come on,
that shit stupid!
That shit
was stupid as fuck.
You know what?
All you niggas sound like
some straight bitches
right now.
That fucking
nerdy-ass white boy
needed that shit.
- [Mellow] Mm-huh.
- He lucky y'all was there.
You were ready
to crash out.
[Dolo] And, Mellow?
What's up?
Watch your fucking tone
with me,
or me and you
gotta chuck 'em,
nigga.
We good?
All right, bruh.
I know
you a gangster, bruh.
you a real nigga.
And when you dealing
with a nigga like me,
I'm as real
as they come.
So we good,
bruh?
- [Mellow] Fuck this shit, bruh.
- [car door slams close]
Fuck that nigga!
[Preach] Bruh, nigga,
you cool off!
- Hey. Hey.
- Man, get your ass in the car!
Come on.
- Y'all niggas just take a--
- [Preach] The fuck you two--
take-- take a hit of the gas--
Shut the fuck up,
Cloudy!
Hey, more gas
for me then, nigga.
[cell phone buzzing]
[continues buzzing]
[keypad beeps]
[clears throat] Yo, what's good?
[Berner over phone]
What are you talking about,
bro? "What's good?"
The pack's not landed yet.
I know you know
what that means.
Yo, they-- they got sent off.
Yo, because--
Don't-- don't worry about it.
Just-- just give it another day.
They gonna arrive
like clockwork.
Bro, I'm not
on your time.
They should've been here
five days ago, minimum.
Yo, because you-- you know
how this mail shit go.
I-I mean, shit,
it probably just got held up.
Just trust me,
give it another day.
It'll land.
And if it don't, look,
- we'll figure something out.
- "We"?
"We'll figure something out"?
Bro, you sent the packs.
If they don't land tomorrow,
I'm gonna need my work
or my cash ASAP.
- All right, I-- I'll make su--
- Figure out this bag, fam.
[whispers] Fuck.
[in normal voice] Fuck!
[sighs]
[uneasy music playing]
What I tell you about
doing that shit?
And what was
all of that about, huh?
Nothin'.
It sure don't seem like nothin'.
Juju, why you gotta act
like that?
I said it wasn't nothing.
- Just leave it at that.
- Uh-uh. Sit down!
I didn't raise you like this.
Sit down.
Now!
We are both hurting,
and-- and I wish
I could just take
all of your pain away,
baby. I do.
We both miss
Elijah.
But you sitting in here
smoking and drinking
all day,
that ain't helping
anything.
And we need
the help.
Lord knows
if your brother
was here,
- he'd be helping us out...
- He's not.
- Elijah ain't here.
- ...right now.
Elijah ain't here,
Ma.
A-and you don't think
I'm helping?
Who you think's
been covering the bills?
How you paying the bills, Juju?
- And what does it matter?
- Ain't no son of mine
selling drugs
out of my house.
I bust my ass
to provide
for you two boys,
so you didn't
have to go out there
and do all that shit.
Then you need
to get out
of my house.
Nah, nah,
you never kicked Slim out
when he was on the block.
Never.
He worked hard
and he changed himself.
There it is.
I knew it was coming.
It always does.
You always comparing us.
Why can't I
just be me, Ma?
That's not good enough
for you?
What the fuck do you think
you're doing around here?
- Boy, you better watch
your tongue.
- Nah, nah!
You throw it in my face
all the fucking time!
You smoking,
you drinking.
You walk up
in this house,
see me,
roll your eyes at me,
go upstairs,
take your little fucking pills.
Sounds like
we both a lot alike.
So, what's up?
Don't you ever
step to me
like that again.
I brought you in this world,
and I will take you out.
You understand me?
- Do you understand me?
- I hear you loud and clear.
All right?
You want me out?
Then fuck it.
[voice breaks]
Fuck it, I'm out.
[Monique sobs]
[door closes]
["Rockin' Up Work"
by San Quinn plays]
♪ Yeah, one ♪
♪ Still ripping my tough
And I'm famous ♪
♪ Why I'm still rocking at work
This is clear, yo ♪
♪ Still ripping my tough
And I'm famous ♪
♪ Why I'm still rocking at work
This is clear, yo ♪
♪ Still ripping my tough
And I'm famous ♪
♪ Why, 'cause I'm rocking
At work, one ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm rocking
♪ 'Cause I'm rocking at work ♪
[song continues indistinctly
on car radio]
[brakes squeal]
[siren wailing in distance]
[song fades out]
[whistle blows]
What's up, Ju?
- Good game?
- Shit.
- What's up?
- What's up, boy?
Yeah, man,
it's intense out here.
You know.
- [players yelling indistinct]
- [car honking]
Um...
How-- how you find me
out here?
[Dolo]
You know, if a nigga
wanna run up on you,
they know
where you at.
Everybody know
where to find you.
Tss, man,
I remember your brother
used to be killing it
out here.
Man, that nigga Slim was
the rawest nigga I know
on that hoop, bruh.
[impressed exhale]
It's fucked up
what happened
to that nigga, man.
Look,
little bro...
I know me and Slim
had our differences...
[clicks tongue]
...but I'm telling you,
bro,
me and dude was tight.
Like,
fuck the differences.
He was my nigga
since we was kids, bro.
But people change.
You seen it,
right?
Yeah.
[Dolo] I've been hearing
a lot of rumors and shit, man.
It's getting hot
out here.
Boys sniffing around,
wondering what the fuck
is going on. Psh.
I just wanna make sure
me and you good.
Don't want nothin'
fucking up our operation.
You feel me?
Matter of fact...
I figured out
that little problem
you had.
Yo, how-- how you know
about that?
[Dolo laughs]
Come on, nigga.
Your little ass don't know
how to mail out shit, right?
[Dolo laughs]
Yeah.
Yo...
Dolo, I owe you one.
Appreciate you,
big cuz.
Don't even trip off
that shit.
It's the least
I can do.
I know y'all got
a lot of shit
going on right now.
[tense music playing]
Plus... I don't want nothin'
fucking up the operation.
I know that
now that your big bro
gone and shit...
you gonna need somebody
to step up in your life.
Somebody to protect you,
guide you,
show you the ropes
of the street shit.
I can be
that person, Ju.
Look, get right
with God,
play your ball,
do whatever it is
that you gotta do
to get your head
back in the game.
We'll see you soon,
right, nigga?
- [Juju] Mm.
- All right, little bro.
[Diego] Bro, what the fuck
is we up here just sitting for?
[Preach] I mean,
what's the holdup?
I got a little dizzy
in the town waiting, bro.
[Diego]
Okay, my fault.
Can you niggas
just relax, man?
Fuck.
That's why.
[Diego] Aw, shit.
This nigga?
What's happening, Ju?
Big money time.
Come on, man. Get in the car.
Let's make this money,
little bro.
I don't wanna start feeling
no type of way about you.
Come on, bro.
[Diego] Man, hurry the fuck up.
[Diego] What's good, bro?
Come on, man.
[engine starts, revs]
♪ Sit down, we gon send it
Round, suck his facial off ♪
♪ Old bro, let it blow
A little drink, he talks ♪
♪ Closed casket, they won't
Even see his face at all ♪
♪ Heard that nigga landin'
On his face ♪
♪ When they made him fall ♪
♪ Follows and fists, 5.56 ♪
♪ Divided on my side
But niggas know ♪
♪ This is my shit
I'm quiet ♪
♪ But I slide, Id rather go ♪
♪ I don't buy hits
Don't gamble with your life ♪
♪ And try to switch
When I'm dicey ♪
♪ We with all that, nigga
We will yank in this bitch ♪
♪ Nigga, fall back, we got
Many coyotes with the sticks ♪
♪ Hit his neck, tryna hit him
In his face, but he lit ♪
♪ When they miss on that skip
But we gon' double back again ♪
♪ We with all that, nigga
We will yank in this bitch ♪
♪ Nigga, fall back, we got
Many coyotes with the sticks ♪
♪ Hit his neck, tryna hit him
In his face, but he live ♪
♪ When they miss on that skip
But we gon' double back again ♪
♪ We with all that ♪
[tires screech]
[song ends]
[Preach speaking, muffled]
[Preach] Just sitting back,
not saying shit, fucking zombie.
And all you do is smoke,
motherfucker.
Give me the weed.
What's wrong
with that, nigga?
[Preach]
Just a high-ass nigga.
You don't get
no fucking money
no more.
- Damn, man.
- Matter of fact,
give-- give me that.
That nigga said,
they're, like,
I be taking bumps.
[Preach] You used to be
a hustler, little nigga.
Now, all your ass do is roll up,
hella cookie and shit.
- Fuck is wrong with you?
- [Cloudy] Okay.
Stop right here, nigga.
- [car door opens]
- [man] Oh, snap.
These niggas,
I'm telling you,
do not give a fuck.
Film that real quick.
[woman] Babe,
is he hitting the window?
- [man] Oh, shit!
- Hey! What the fuck?
- Do you see this shit? Oh.
- This shit is crazy.
Fuck up, nigga.
[hip-hop music playing
on speakers]
[Cloudy] Hold on, hold on.
Right here, right here.
[car door opens]
- [man] Crazy.
- [woman] Oh, hell no!
[man] Bippers is everywhere.
They don't give a fuck
'cause it's broad daylight.
You gotta be cool.
- Can't leave shit in the car.
- [woman] Nothin'.
- [chuckles]
- [Cloudy] Hold on, hold on.
Let me see.
Right here, right here.
Hold on, nigga.
Let me eat that.
[Preach] Go on, then.
[man] They do not give a fuck
out here.
- [woman] Oh, shit.
- [man] I was telling you.
I just told you that.
- [woman] Ooh.
- [car alarm wailing]
- Do you see this shit?
- [man] Damn.
Shit is crazy in the Bay.
I'm telling you. Frisco, Oakley,
the whole Bay is bipping.
[woman] What we gonna do now?
- [car door closes]
- [Cloudy] I'm over it, nigga.
And I'm older than you, nigga.
And I'm smoking
at the same damn time, nigga.
Okay, nigga. I see you got it
in you a little bit, huh?
Still acting? Huh, motherfucker?
♪ I love nigga city ♪
♪ Trail shit
Into the steel clique ♪
[music ends]
[uneasy music playing]
[Preach] Hey,
what's the worst bunge
y'all been in?
[Diego and Cloudy] Uh...
[Diego]
That's a hard choice.
[Diego] 'Cause I done had
a couple a weak bitches...
[Cloudy]
Silly as shit.
Uh, one day went
to the fish market.
- [Cloudy] Oh, you was--
- [Preach] Whoa, whoa, shit!
- [officer] Police!
- [sirens wailing]
[officers yelling indistinct]
[officer 2] Get down
on your knees!
Come on, everybody.
Come on, hit concrete.
Let's go, everybody.
What's up, Darnell?
[chuckles]
[Detective Sanchez]
What the fuck
you smiling for, huh?
We about to take your ass in.
Anyway...
Looks like we got Tramane,
got Mellow, Derek, and Diego.
Wait, who's that over there?
Julian,
is it?
Or would you rather
I called you "Juju"?
What a stupid name.
You must think
you're pretty slick,
Darnell,
stealing cars
left and right.
[sighs] I don't even know
what the fuck
y'all talking about, man.
I really don't appreciate
your guys
roughing us up
like that,
'cause now...
my clothes stink
like fucking bacon.
[Detective Jennings]
Mm-hmm.
That's my favorite meal.
You know, Elijah's murder
wasn't just some random act.
- Oh, really?
- [door opens]
Never took you
for a killer, though.
Thank you,
Detective Sanchez.
Let's see
what we won.
- [door closes]
- Oh, oh, yeah.
Glamour shots.
How about
that one?
Oh, there's a winner
right there.
Oh, there's another one.
Now, word on the street
is this guy was your friend.
How about that one?
Yeah, man, that was my boy.
Why y'all showing me
this shit, man?
What the fuck?
Fun fact, 30% of all homicides
are perpetrated by someone
who knows the victim.
Someone wanted
your brother dead.
Can you think of anybody
who'd wanna harm him?
The casings
that did this
are linked to a gun
in our possession.
[Detective Jennings]
These are the shell casings from
your brother's murder scene.
About two weeks ago,
some norteño
got picked up
in San Jose.
Crazy thing,
he had a gun on him.
But we sat on it...
did some more digging.
- [thud]
- Turns out, his story holds up.
He didn't kill your brother.
Dirty bitches took
my last paper cookie,
my nigga.
Hey, man, somebody tell me
what the fuck just happened
- back there.
- [Cloudy] Yo, why the fuck
is they asking us
about Slim?
Yo, everybody chill
the fuck out, man!
Let me think.
[object scrapes]
You good?
I really hope you little niggas
was listening
and paying attention.
Them people
don't got shit on us.
If they did,
they would've came,
kicked door,
we all would've been gone
already.
[Juju] They was asking
about my brother's murder.
Like we some
motherfucking suspects.
You a suspect, nigga?
That's what
they set out to do.
They gotta ask
questions.
- Somebody gotta take
the rap, nigga.
- Nah, nah, nigga.
They wasn't pressing
about no fucking bips.
They were asking about a murder!
They asked me about Slim,
like I fuckin' know!
- And what did you say?
- Nigga, what the fuck
you think I said?
Then what the fuck
you asking me for then,
nigga?
Look... that shit weird
as fuck.
That's all I'm saying.
So, what you gotta say now?
Hey, fuck off of me!
The fuck is wrong
with you, man?
[Diego]
Let little nigga go, bruh.
[Cloudy] What the fuck?
What the fuck is wrong
with you, little nigga?
They gettin'
in your head, man!
This is what
they train to do!
Get in
your fucking head!
Seem like to me
they doing a great job.
[Juju] I don't need
this shit.
[Dolo] Go on,
get the fuck up
outta here, nigga.
That pussy-ass shit.
What's up, nigga?
You keep giving me
all these fucking funny looks!
Oh, I get it.
You wanna be top dog,
huh, nigga?
You can't be that, man.
That's me!
[exhales]
You know what?
I been too fucking cool
with you little niggas.
Putting you little niggas on.
Got you making money
with the team.
Last motherfucker
that tried to come play
with me,
it ain't go too well
for that nigga.
So I suggest
all you little niggas
think about that.
'Cause I don't give a fuck
about none of you niggas.
- Just like that?
- Yeah, nigga, just like that.
Who the fuck you think
that you talking to, man?
- [Cloudy] Hey, hey, hey.
- Just be cool, bruh.
Hey.
Y'all niggas, bro,
might as well chuck 'em,
'cause all this testosterone,
bro, you niggas have,
niggas either need
a good meal
or some good pussy.
I'm just saying
though, bro.
You niggas need to squash this
'cause this shit is embarr--
Fuck this shit, bro.
Shit, man, I'm out.
Bitch, where the fuck
you going?
I ain't dismiss
your ass yet.
Do, you may got these
other little niggas fooled,
I'm on point
with my shit,
you feel me?
Don't worry,
bro.
Ayo, fuck them
backdoor niggas, bro.
[annoyed exhale]
Yo, you trippin'.
You know I know
who killed your brother
and you damn sure know
who killed your brother, man.
[sighs]
You could play dumb
all you want...
but that bitch-ass nigga
got somethin' coming for him.
Watch your body,
bro.
[Cloudy] Look at that whip
that just pulled up.
[Diego] Who the fuck is that?
- Wow, that's me.
Where my gloves at, bruh?
- [Juju scoffs]
Are you sure
we're good here, baby?
[H-Town chuckles]
Yeah, girl.
What you mean?
Baby, ain't nobody
finna fuck with me.
We good
anywhere we go.
Ju.
Since you act like
you about "this life"...
[chuckles]
...you wanna be
a gangster...
let's get
this big league money in, nigga.
Look, I'm gonna tell you
one thing about Slim.
That nigga
was never scared.
I heard
this little place smack
right here.
We'll go hit this up,
then we hit up Skee.
Come on.
Let's go,
nigga.
[Preach] What we waitin' on
then, nigga?
- [Diego] Come on.
- What we waitin' on?
[Juju] It's me.
It's me. I'm on it.
Excuse me.
Ma'am.
[H-Town] Baby,
what do you want?
Let's just order
two birria tacos.
[glass shattering]
- [Juju] Go, go, go, go!
- [Diego] Go, go, go!
[H-Town] Hey!
Hey, motherfuckers!
- [tires screeching]
- Hey!
[woman]
I fucking told you!
- What?
Get me my fucking phone!
- Wait, hold on!
- I don't have your phone!
- Give me my fucking phone!
- Oh, my God.
- Get the fuck in the car!
Get in the car!
[Cloudy] Hey, Diego,
slow the fuck down!
Relax, nigga.
[engine revving]
[tires screech]
[engine stops]
Hey, bruh,
that fucking Mexican nigga
almost killed your ass.
What's the nigga got,
some bricks or somethin'?
Nigga doofing to be the plug.
Why was
that nigga Diego cousin
running fast as hell?
- [laughter]
- [Diego] Got me fucked up.
[Juju] Oh, shit.
[tense music playing]
- [Cloudy] Oh, shit!
- [Diego] What?
We hit! We hit, nigga!
Hit for what? Some work?
Fi-- fifty, sixty.
Nigga, this is like a--
like a couple 100,000 at least!
[Diego] Man, y'all niggas lying.
This shit--
You niggas ain't lying.
Let's go inside. Let's go count
this shit up right quick.
- [men cheering]
- [Diego] Stop playing!
- Stop playing!
- [Dolo clapping]
[men clamoring]
[Juju] What?
Louis V belt, nigga!
[Diego] Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, look!
- Velvet room, bottles on me...
- We made it!
- [Juju laughing] Yo!
- ...and I need Tone, bitch!
- We made it.
- I was in that fucking window--
♪ You can take a nigga
Out the ghetto ♪
♪ But you can't take
The ghetto out of me ♪
- [Juju] Nigga, what?
- Let's throw one up.
- Niggas really build like that.
- I told you.
- Nigga, what?
- I told you, nigga.
[Preach]
Hey, let's throw one up.
Let's throw one up.
- It's time to go up
with my niggas.
- Let's go!
- Time to go up.
- Let's go, boy!
- [Preach chuckles]
- [Diego] Come on now.
Uh, uh.
You're my brothers, man.
- [Diego] Love you.
- [Preach] Preach on that.
Let me make a toast
to my niggas right quick.
- [Diego] Come on, bruh.
Come on.
- Ah, yeah.
- [Juju] Come on, bro.
- Toast to new life, man.
Toast to
my motherfucking niggas.
Nigga, we just scored,
nigga.
This a real splash right here.
Let's go, baby.
[Cloudy] Money, nigga,
more life.
- [Dolo] Let's go, baby.
- [Preach] Get it all in. Ah!
[Dolo] Mm.
[Diego] Yeah.
Why y'all niggas act like
y'all got half a ticket
- in the motherfucking bank?
- Pop it open, nigga!
- Pop that shit open!
- Pop it open!
[Preach] Hey, nigga said,
Velvet room.
Let's run, nigga! What?
[Cloudy] The earth saying,
"I'm drinking too."
- [Dolo] Diego.
- [Preach] I don't give a fuck.
Oh, my nigga,
let me see that!
- [Cloudy] Gotta like that now.
- Who, who this?
- New-- new phone who?
- [Preach] Ah, boy, who this?
[overlapping chatter]
Juju.
That's for you.
Preach,
that's for you.
Excuse me, my nigga.
Who is this for?
That's your cut, nigga.
What you mean?
Where the rest
of it?
I-I just pulled
this shit.
I thought
we might be splitting it.
Splitting it?
What the fuck
do you mean?
You would be sitting
at the house mourning
right now, right, nigga?
And what about
them fucking packs?
I'm getting real sick
of saving your little ass.
If I didn't tell
you motherfuckers
to bop that load,
none of this
would ever happen.
So, I don't see
what the issue is.
[Preach] My nigga,
you-- you keep smiling, bruh.
All right, bruh.
Good joke, nigga.
Good joke. Where the rest
of that shit at, bruh?
- [Cloudy] He be playing.
- Bruh, come on, bruh.
Look, Do, I-I think we--
I just thought--
Thought what?
Thought what, nigga?
[chuckles]
That's your problem, Ju.
Stop thinking,
nigga.
Start doing.
That's what
you been doing.
[Dolo puffs]
You niggas
some weird little niggas, bruh.
You know what?
G-O-D.
I'm cool off you little niggas.
Fuck y'all.
[bag scrapes]
[zipper zips]
Come on, Diego.
Fuck these niggas.
- Oh, and you know what?
- [Preach] Hold on, hold on.
Neither one
of you little niggas
better not call
my fucking phone.
Nigga, don't text me.
None of that shit.
Unless it's about
some real shit.
Have fun
with that little ten ball.
Hit me when y'all ready
for the Velvet room though.
[Preach grumbling]
- These niggas
is always cheating.
- [Trish giggles]
- [chuckles]
- [Trish] You're the cheater.
I'm nice.
[Trish] I bet you
I could beat you.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
- Babe, teach me.
- Hold on, hold on. Hold on.
[buzzing]
[continues buzzing]
- Yo.
- [Diego over phone] Bruh.
- What's up?
- You fucking missed out, bruh.
- The fuck
is you talking about, dog?
- Get off the phone.
I'm talking about
we scored, my nigga.
Man, we splashed
on something
so crazy.
Man. Anyways,
check it out.
I was really calling you
to let you know
I got a play
for you, bruh.
Well, for us.
You know
what the fuck I mean.
Same shit.
[clicks tongue]
Man, hello?
Yo, is you
even fucking listening?
What you--
what you call me for, bruh?
All right,
remember them AirTags
- we slapped on them whips?
- [kisses]
What about 'em?
Come on.
Yeah, well, I been tracking
one of them motherfuckers.
One of 'em
out your way.
That's really why
I was calling you, bruh.
Go hit that shit.
We'll split it
down the middle.
[Mellow]
Um...
- No.
- No, no. I--
I ain't fucking
with that shit, bro.
- I'm cool.
- Yeah, he not fucking with it.
Don't let her speak
for you, bruh.
Ain't nobody speak
for me, bro. Chill. Hey.
All right, look,
I was really calling
- trying to throw my dog a bone.
- All right.
So we gonna run up
a fucking bag
or you gonna go broke
in the booty, nigga?
[sighs] Yo, just send the--
just send the info, all right?
- Ahh! That's my dog!
- Are you serious?
- About to send the drops.
Say less.
- Hurry up, bro.
Don't go.
I might not be here
when you get back.
[tense music playing]
[Dolo] What's up,
motherfucker?
Don't expect
to see me here,
huh, nigga?
[tires screeching]
[Preach] Dolo,
we need that casa amigos
and them freak hoes
and everything.
Yeah. Hey.
That's on you, bruh.
Come on, cop it.
[Cloudy] The last bottle
for the last two that we have...
[Preach] Hey, you got
the bread, bruh. Come on.
Let's get it, bruh.
[bottles clinking]
Hey, nigga.
What the fuck?
Hey, motherfucker!
Nigga, you deaf,
dumb, or stupid?
[man] What the fuck is this?
You wanna die
out here?
Nigga, you better
chill out, cousin.
[Skee] I don't know
why the fuck you acting like
we ain't got
no problem, nigga.
Nigga only been home for--
for fucking two weeks, bruh.
Then I get a call
that my nigga got hit
by the wharf
last night, bruh.
So, where was y'all at
last night, huh?
We was in Richmond,
fucking with some hoes,
making some money.
[Skee] Hey, bruh,
you keep smiling and shit
like this shit
is a joke,
my nigga.
The money
that you took, nigga,
is me
and Tone money, bruh.
You taking money from him,
you taking money from me,
my nigga.
You young niggas
be with that snake shit, bruh.
Backdoor niggas,
bruh.
- I'm gonna make some calls--
- Hey, hey.
Nigga, please,
nigga.
I hear you talking, nigga.
That's all you do is talk, bruh.
Man, let's get up
out of here, man.
Quit playing
with these old
suck-ass niggas, bruh.
- I'm gonna make
some calls for you, man.
- [Skee] Nigga.
Nigga, fuck calling, nigga.
- Bring that motherfucking
money, nigga.
- [chuckles]
- I got you. I got you.
- I'll be back, nigga.
[Skee] Yeah, all right.
- [Dolo] Yeah.
- [Juju] Hey.
Hey, y'all see this?
[Preach]
What the fuck?
What's--
They say Mellow is dead, nigga.
Where the fuck
was he at? Shit.
This shit can't be real
right now. Shit.
[Juju] Pick up the phone!
Hey, Diego, didn't you just text
Mellow last night?
- What was he on, bruh?
- Nigga didn't answer.
Do.
Do, nigga? You deaf?
Who we on, nigga?
What we doin'?
You niggas ain't tell nobody
that we hit last night, right?
[Cloudy] Naw, man.
Of course not, nigga.
Okay, cool.
Then I suggest
all you little goofy-ass niggas
keep your
fucking mouth shut
and watch
what's said.
I got this.
[Juju] Fuck you mean
you got this?
You wanna know the truth,
little nigga?
The reason
your fucking brother got got
is 'cause the nigga
got caught slipping.
And Mellow?
That bitch-ass nigga
got a mouth on him.
Probably ran into
the wrong motherfucker,
and they smoked
his ass.
Oh, check this out.
You know Skee?
Fuck Skee.
Any niggas step in my way,
they gonna get it.
I don't give a fuck.
Any nigga play with me,
they gonna die.
- That's how I'm rocking.
- [Preach] Nah, nigga, nah, nah.
Fuck all that shit, nigga.
This way too close
to home, bruh.
Nigga, it's Mellow,
bruh, Mellow.
Nigga, how we know
that nigga Skee and his people
ain't playing with us, bruh?
How we know
they ain't off Mellow, bruh,
trying to get at us?
We know how them niggas
get down.
They the real
backdoor boys, nigga!
Let's get up
out of here, Diego.
Nigga, and where the fuck
y'all going?
I'm trying to tell you, nigga,
there's some weird shit
going on, bro.
I'm trying to tell you.
This man is fucked,
nigga!
[Skee] Man, I just pulled up
to the shop, bruh.
My fucking worker talking about
he got fucking COVID.
And I had to get up
this morning, bruh.
He coughing and shit
all on people, bruh.
When he coming back?
I'm not trying
to be here all day.
What's up,
Skee?
Man, what the fuck? Hey, bro,
let me call you back, bruh.
This little ass nigga.
What the fuck is you doing, bro?
The fuck you know
what's going on?
What the fuck you doing
at my shop, my nigga?
Relax, nigga. Goddamn.
To relax, nigga?
How can I relax, bruh?
You know
what's going on.
You know a young nigga like me
keep his ear to the streets.
Is-- So what you hearing?
I fuck around
and I found out
who hit your folks.
You serious, bruh?
You found out?
If you found out, hey,
let me call the hyenas, nigga.
Get on these niggas' head,
bruh.
These niggas
got me fucked up.
- What the fuck?
- It was me, nigga.
The fuck you do? Hey, bro,
what the fuck you doing, nigga?
- [gunshots]
- [Skee] Ahh!
[groans]
Time for you old niggas
to get the fuck out the way.
[Skee grunts weakly]
[ominous tone]
Motherfucking
backdoor niggas, man.
That nigga's crazy.
But you know what?
I got something for that.
Listen,
y'all niggas trust me?
You ain't
even gotta ask
that shit.
Hit for motherfucking
half a ticket
the other night.
Y'all know
whose money that was.
Shit, we get
that shit back,
we with the big dogs.
Man,
fuck Dolo.
Fuck all them
shady-ass niggas, bruh.
Let's get
what's ours.
[softly]
Here.
You're my nigga,
man.
["Call Me" by Berner plays]
♪ When you need someone
To talk to ♪
♪ Someone to fuck you ♪
♪ Call me... ♪
- [Evelyn] We don't have
to do this in here.
- [Juju] What's up, Eve?
Tone around?
No.
What's up, honey?
[Juju]
Need a favor.
I don't talk business
at the bar.
Follow me.
[woman slurping]
[continues slurping]
[knocking on door]
[whispers]
The fuck?
[scoffs]
- [thud]
- [indistinct chatter]
Yo!
Who the fuck is that?
...fucked!
[Diego] There he go right there.
[Dolo] What's up
with it, Tone?
[Tone] Been trying
to reach you all day.
Man, you heard
Skee got shot?
He in the hospital
right now.
[Dolo]
Damn.
I hope he pull through.
Shit, us too.
Crazy timing too 'cause our plug
just got hit last night
- for 500K.
- [Diego whistles softly]
Say it was a little gray car,
little dude with
a camo face mask and shit.
- That wasn't y'all, right?
- Tss.
Hell nah, man.
[Diego] I hope it wasn't Juju.
Half a ticket, bruh?
Shit, we'd be in Cabo right now
- going crazy.
- Fired up.
Talking about "toes in the sand"
type shit. [chuckles]
But you know
we fuck with you, Tone.
You know we keep our ears
to the street shit.
About to make a couple calls
and shit.
I'll let you know what I hear.
Okay.
Speaking of Juju,
he out here running around
with these boys from the UK...
trying to put a box play
together and shit.
And the boys he with, man,
iced the fuck out.
Bust down everything, man.
Straight lacking.
What you trying to do?
I'm gonna have my partners
take him to the Velvet,
and follow him back
to they spot.
[Diego] Mmm.
- Can y'all handle that?
- Hell yeah.
Let's go.
Fifty-fifty.
The AP alone, worth it all.
Bread just a little cherry
on top, man.
- Man, come on.
- Let's go.
- We need that.
- All right, let's get it.
Let's eat then, man.
[Dolo]
Let's get it.
[Diego] Come on, bruh, come on.
[Dolo]
Come on, man.
You know
what time it is?
Hey, um...
how many people we with?
[Tone] Two,
maybe three.
- [Dolo] Hmm.
- [Tone] You can handle 'em?
[Dolo] Yeah.
Yeah, we do, dog.
- [Tone] Okay, all right. Later.
- [Dolo] Yeah, for sure.
What's up, D man?
You good?
- [D] All good, boy.
- All right, for sure.
- All right, bro.
- Yeah? All right, bro.
- [Dolo sighs]
- [door closes]
- [Dolo] That shit felt weird.
- Weird as fuck.
You think them niggas know?
Tss. I don't know, bruh.
[Dolo] I'm gonna need you to go
to the spot and clean house.
[Diego] Yeah?
Tell all the homies keep
they head on a swivel, bruh.
- This shit gettin' weird.
- It's good.
[Diego] Hey, bruh, check it out.
D on his way to go link up
with Juju right now
at Tone's spot, bruh.
Shit getting funky, my nigga.
Yo.
Tell the homies
at the Grove spot too, bruh,
stay on toes,
for real, for real.
Like, Tone and Los pulled up
on some weird-ass shit
tonight, bruh.
I'm about to clean house
over here real quick.
I'mma link with y'all niggas
in a bit.
♪ Same nigga ♪
♪ Ain't nothing changing
My bank bill ♪
♪ Dough dealer
I pull the Porsche out... ♪
[song continues indistinctly]
[ominous music playing]
- [tires squeal]
- [guns cock]
[bullets clinking]
[ominous music continues]
[cell phone chimes]
[window shatters]
[tense musical stinger]
[siren wailing in distance]
["Mardi Gras" by Kool John
and P-Lo plays]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ I hit it from the back
I'm pullin' on her front toes ♪
♪ Hey, uh, no, I cannot be
Your man, goddamn ♪
♪ Touchin' green
Feelin' like I'm Sam, I am ♪
♪ Ten toes, never sit
On business, I stand, uh... ♪
What's up?
Where the fuck
is everybody?
Nice to see you too,
Darnell.
I'm glad
you could show up.
Look, I had to send 'em
on a little errand
for the girls.
They'll be back
soon.
Where your man at?
Where Tone?
Nigga, this is
my establishment.
The fuck
you mean?
I run
this shit.
I don't need no man
to run my business.
All right, man.
I got you. Relax.
Why don't you go wait
in the VIP?
I'll let you know
when they arrive.
All right,
bet.
♪ Go crazy ♪
[song ends]
["Busy Body" by Berner plays]
♪ She's so incredible ♪
♪ Ain't, no doubt about it ♪
♪ Might let her ride it ♪
♪ Everybody know
That you a busy body, baby ♪
♪ Bounce with it
Get it, get it ♪
♪ She's so dangerous, yeah ♪
♪ Bounce with it
Get it, get it ♪
♪ She's so dangerous, yeah ♪
♪ Can't lie
She got a whole lotta game ♪
♪ Most of these squares
Can't hang ♪
♪ Not with a bitch like that ♪
♪ She gon' have you
Spendin' stacks ♪
♪ If you tryna hit that cat ♪
♪ You gotta pay for it ♪
♪ And then fuck her ♪
♪ But you don't mind payin' ♪
♪ 'Cause you a sucker ♪
♪ I heard she got fucked
Last night too ♪
♪ It's just what some
Of these bitches do ♪
♪ If niggas like you
Keep cakin' 'em ♪
♪ Niggas like me
Gon' keep breakin' 'em ♪
♪ And if these bitches
Don't get it, I'm shakin' 'em ♪
♪ But not you, shoppin' is
Where you takin' 'em ♪
♪ Let a real nigga push up
On that lil' bitch... ♪
Hey, baby.
You wanna dance?
Nah, I'm straight.
I'm good.
What about
a drink, then?
- Bitch, get the fuck
off my lap!
- [yelps]
Well, then,
fuck you, nigga!
You probably broke
as fuck anyways.
Get the fuck out of here, man.
Where the fuck
these niggas at, man?
[foreboding music plays]
[exasperated sigh]
[clamoring]
[people screaming]
[ominous music playing]
[Dolo]
Is you fucking serious?
Better get that shit
out my face
before you fuck around
and make me mad.
This motherfucker.
Nigga, what the fuck
you gonna do?
I'm the nigga
who put you on!
I showed you
how to make money, nigga.
You finna kill me?
Quit fucking playing.
Elijah told me
you were grimy.
All you think about
is yourself.
And I had your back.
[chuckles]
You wanna know
the complete,
100% honest truth, nigga?
Fucking brother
was a piece of shit.
Nigga turned his back on me
when I needed him the most.
After all the shit
I did for him.
When they used to pick on
a nigga at the ball court,
who the fuck you think
had his back?
It was me!
You think I'm about to let
the nigga get up and leave
after I put him
in position?
Fuck no.
Your bitch-ass brother
walked his hoe ass
in my spot,
trying to disrespect me
in front of my folks.
How you think
that make me look?
that make me look, nigga?
Put that fucking gun down,
nigga.
You ain't no killer,
If you put
that fucking gun down,
I'mma pick it up
and I'mma kill you.
Then after I kill you,
and we smoke
your ass...
I'mma go fuck
your brother bitch.
Then after I fuck
that little stupid bitch,
I'm about to go fuck
your mama!
[tense musical stinger]
[ominous musical stinger]
[ominous tone]
[tense music playing]
Never would've took you
for a killer, little homie.
But I appreciate you taking
matters in your own hands.
Look, I ain't gonna lie, man.
Dolo was a problem,
and he needed to go.
But you put a lot of heat
on my club on top of yourself.
Look, Tone,
that nigga was on one.
All right?
I had to move fast.
I-I went up to the spot.
I-I talked to Evelyn.
- She said it was good. I--
- She would let some shit
like that go down.
She thinks we could sell
a Blanco or some shit.
[chuckles]
Know what, man?
It is what it is.
That spot's been dried up
for some years.
Probably time to find a new way
to clean this money anyways.
[Juju]
So, we good?
[zipper zips]
[bag thuds]
[sighs]
I know what you went through
to get this money.
At first glance,
huh, it looked
a little light.
But the truth is,
we move trucks from here
to Houston to Virginia
to the A.
So, yeah...
we're good.
See, what you doing now,
that's lowlife bum shit.
Look at Tone.
Look at Skee.
That's real business.
The way I see it,
me and you,
we already in business.
So, let me ask you something.
You ready to level up or what?
Yeah.
What's that look like?
[door closes]
What's up, Ju?
[Tone] Looks like we still got
a mess to clean up.
But I'mma get with you soon.
Out-of-town money's
like blow money, baby.
Look, man, all you need to do
is stay out the way, lay low,
tell your little homies
to keep their mouths shut.
We gonna handle
the rest.
Skee.
[door opens, closes]
["Barney (More Crime)"
by The Jacka plays]
♪ Feelin' the pain, baby
You know what I'm sayin'? ♪
♪ You want some of that pain ♪
♪ Super Silver haze ♪
♪ Some of that purple stuff ♪
♪ Purple boy ♪
♪ Smokin' a stick
Of that Barney ♪
♪ But not the purple dinosaur ♪
♪ That shit
That niggas dyin' for ♪
♪ Shit my niggas ridin' on ♪
♪ Sav wit the windows up ♪
♪ See the smoke pour out ♪
♪ Soon as I open the door ♪
♪ Soon as I go to the store ♪
♪ Voices like
"Whoa! Who got it?" ♪
♪ "You know
Who got it, nigga" ♪
♪ Summertime comin' up ♪
♪ Can't breathe without it ♪
♪ Bring the Hpnotiq
Bring the heam ♪
♪ Mix that shit
That turn green ♪
♪ Now break down the purple ♪
♪ It's softly rough
Milwaukee Bucks ♪
♪ I'm from the place
Where they grow that stuff ♪
♪ You got your girl
In the clutch ♪
♪ Just give me a light
I'll take that bitch ♪
♪ If she ain't give me head
All night ♪
♪ Sellin' dope is cool
But rap is on my mind ♪
♪ It's hard to do them both
And get my bread
At the same time ♪
♪ High as fuck off purple
Man, I'm out my mind ♪
♪ Gotta grab my strap
Boy, it's time to do
Some more crime ♪
♪ Sellin' dope is cool
But rap is on my mind ♪
♪ It's hard to do them both
And get my bread
At the same time ♪
♪ High as fuck off purple
Man, I'm out my mind ♪
♪ Gotta grab my strap
Boy, it's time to do ♪
- ♪ Some more crime ♪
- ♪ And all my hoes say ♪
♪ "Jack, you're my soul
Inspiration ♪
♪ Even though you sold crack
Across the nation" ♪
♪ Caught the cases
Kept me quiet like meditation ♪
♪ I say, "Baby
I'm just really wastin'" ♪
♪ A lot of breath on you
For the sport ♪
♪ You think I'm nice
But that's really not me ♪
♪ I live the life
That you never gon' see ♪
♪ Niggas fight
They don't war like me ♪
♪ It's the last of my kind
There's no more like me ♪
♪ Tryna make it on the street ♪
♪ Is like swimmin'
Through the sea ♪
♪ Tryna make it
To the other side of life ♪
♪ My young nigga say
He tired of life ♪
♪ And now realize
He's addicted to the white ♪
♪ Got sucked up by the war ♪
♪ Tryna make things right
Right ♪
♪ He said, he said, he said
"It's rainin' outside ♪
♪ And the difference
Between us ♪
♪ Is a white bus
Wit cages inside ♪
♪ When I come home
Still face the cop cars ♪
♪ Wit gauges inside
Yo, on the real, it's yo rap ♪
♪ Is what kept me alive" ♪
♪ Sellin' dope is cool
But rap is on my mind ♪
♪ It's hard to do them both
And get my bread
At the same time ♪
♪ High as fuck off purple
Man, I'm out my mind ♪
♪ Gotta grab my strap
Boy, it's time to do
Some more crime ♪
♪ Sellin' dope is cool
But rap is on my mind ♪
♪ It's hard to do them both
And get my bread
At the same time ♪
♪ High as fuck off purple
Man, I'm out my mind ♪
♪ Gotta grab my strap
Boy, it's time to do
Some more crime ♪
[song fades out]